<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stumps11</string><!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="AboutUs">Welcome to your one stop destination for fantasy sports. Here, at Stumps11 you will get ample opportunities to earn money by utilizing the knowledge in the field of sports. We allow our users to enjoy cricket, make fantasy teams and win real cash daily. Just select the match you want to play in, join the contest you wish to compete in, create a virtual team from the set of on field players, and boom you are all set to go into the real of Real fantasy.Stumps11 is the fastest-growing fantasy sports platform where you get the best fantasy games at your fingertips. We offer the best gaming experience to our users and help them to enhance their skills by creating a learning environment that facilitates practice. Started as a platform merely dedicated to fantasy cricket leagues. The fantasy platform of Stumps11 is revolutionizing the web gaming industry with its unique and innovative product offering. Users not only get a chance to fulfill their dreams by making the best use of their knowledge of the game but also hone their expertise.We at Stumps11 also offer a safe and secured platform for our users to keep their confidential information intact. We understand our users and serve them with the best features to strengthen their experience with us. In recent times, fantasy cricket sites have gained a lot of traction, and Stumps11 is trying to build trust on such fantasy platforms with its top notch performance and attentive service. Join India’s best fantasy cricket app and become a part of the biggest sports community.</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay1">Stumps11 is a Game of Skill where you create a team of real players for an upcoming match and compete with other fans for big prizes.</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay2">Your team earns points based on your players’ performances in the real-life match, so make sure you make the right choices!</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay3">1. Select A Match</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay4">Stumps11 hosts games across many different sports. Click on an upcoming match you want to play and keep an eye on the match deadline.</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay5">2. Create Your Teams</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay6">Use your knowledge of sports to pick a team within a budget of 100 credits who you think will score the most points for the selected match.</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay7">What are credits?
Credits are the cost of a player. In-form and star players typically cost more credits, while inexperienced or non-regular players cost less.</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay8">3. Join Contests</string>
    <string name="HowToPlay9">We have many different contest formats for you to join. Choose between free and paid contests, or even create a new private contest just for you and your friends. You play your way!</string>
    <string name="Legality">Stumps11 takes excessive care to comply with all the central and state legislation in India to ensure the safety of all our users. Every contest on our platform is delicately designed to comply with all the applicable regulations and statues in India. Below are the critical points from an Indian government’s judgment particularly regarding Stumps11’s game. A challenge to this discernment was also dismissed by the Supreme Court of India:\n"
"The court, in its ruling, stated that playing the Stumps11 game involves substantial skill, judgement and circumspection and that success on Stumps11 arises out of user\'s exercise considerable knowledge,attention, and judgement.\n"
"The court also affirmed that the element of skill holds away on the outcome of the Stumps11 game which follows the following format:\n"
"1. Participants/players/users have to draft a team consisting of at least the same number of players as playing in the real life sports team (for e.g. 11 players in cricket).\n"
"2. All contests are active and run for at least the duration of an actual sports match.\n"
"3. No team changes are permitted after the commencement of a match.\n"
"On this basis, the court adjourned that playing on Stumps11 constitutes a ‘game of mere skill’, which makes the Stumps11 game exempt from all the provisions of the Public Gambling Act 1867 (PGA)\n"
"Eventually, the court held that the Stumps11 game is a legal business activity protected under Article 19(1) (g) of the Constitution of India.</string>
    <string name="Privacy1">Our Privacy is Important</string>
    <string name="Privacy2">We provide online Fantasy Cricket game on Stumps11 for our Users’ entertainment in an absolutely safe, secure and trustworthy environment. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our Users. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect from our Users, how we use their information, and what choices are available to our Users in this regard.This Privacy Policy forms part of our Website’s Terms of Service. Stumps11 respects your privacy and assures you that any information provided by you to Stumps11 is fully protected and will be used according to this Privacy Policy. To play game of Fantasy Cricket offered on Stumps11, you may have to provide certain information to us.</string>
    <string name="Privacy3">The Information We Collect</string>
    <string name="Privacy4">You are required to register with us to become our User and access our games. We collect the personal information of our Users. Examples of this include Users phone numbers. If you do not provide us with the required information, you may not be able to access our Games and other Services. We also collect information other than your personal information, such as your IP address. Such information is not associated with your personal information and cannot be linked to you personally. We may use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the Website, track Users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Stumps11.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this Website. We will not sell, share, or rent our Users’ information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="Privacy5">Usage of the Information Collected</string>
    <string name="Privacy6">Stumps11 does not disclose your personal information to any third party without your express permission. However, by registering on our Website or App, you grant us permission to use and share your personal information as stated in this Privacy Policy. We may need to disclose your information when required by law. We use your personal information to improve our Services and enhance your experience on our Website as well as to notify you of our new Fantasy Cricket offers, Products and Services. Your personal information may be shared with the sponsors and suppliers of prizes for our winners.Stumps11 uses a fool proof security system to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of User information. Stumps11 is not responsible for any activity that takes place in your account.</string>
    <string name="Privacy7">Cookies</string>
    <string name="Privacy8">When you visit our Website or use our App, cookies may be left in your computer or phone. A cookie is a small text file that uniquely identifies your browser and which is assigned by the servers of Stumps11.com. It may be used to personalize your experience on Stumps11.com. Additionally, it may be used for authentication, game management and security purposes. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you other than the data you choose to share with us.Cookies may also be assigned by the advertisers of Stumps11 when you click on any of the advertisements shown on Stumps11.com. In such an event, the cookies are controlled by these advertisers and not by us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you wish. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our Products and Services.</string>
    <string name="Privacy9">Your Consent</string>
    <string name="Privacy10">By registering on our Website or App, you give your express consent for the collection and use of your personal information by Stumps11.com and its partners and affiliates. From time to time, we may change our methods of collecting information and modify our Privacy Policy. We will post such changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Make sure that you stay updated on our Privacy Policy revisions.Stumps11 asserts that this Privacy Policy is only a description of its operation regarding User information. This Privacy Policy does not create any legal rights in your favour or in favour of any other person, group or organization. Stumps11 reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice.</string>
    <string name="Agreement">We advise you to read our Terms of Service carefully and understand them well. All the clauses in the Terms of Service of Stumps11 are delineated below and included in the medium of reference that can be accessed by clicking on the related links. You should make sure that you have read and understood our Agreement, including our Terms of Service, well before becoming a member of Stumps11. By registering on Stumps11, you agree to follow our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and Game Rules. You are completely bound by our Agreement in any instance when you choose to use our Services or Games or software. We reserve the right to modify and amend our Terms of Service at any time. When we make any changes to our Terms of Service, we shall inform you about the revisions by sending you a notice at your email address registered with us. We shall also update such changes on our Website. We may make changes to our Terms of Service in order to review or change any of our Policies and Game Rules. If you do not agree to the changes made, you may cease your use of our Services of online Fantasy Cricket games by informing us that you have deleted your account. If you continue to use our Services after any amendments or changes, it shall be assumed that you have accepted the changes made in the Agreement and you agree to our new Terms.</string>
    <string name="Warrenty">Stumps11 aims to provide information that is accurate, complete, and reliable at the time of publishing or posting it. However, Stumps11 makes no representations about the correctness, completeness or suitability of any information published on its Website or contained in its documents. All the information and related graphics are provided on an "as is" basis without warranty of any kind, express or implied. Stumps11 hereby disclaims all warranties with regard to such information, including all implied warranties and conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement. Regardless of Stumps11\'s efforts to provide its Users with the Services of the highest quality, Stumps11 does not provide Users with any warranty or representation whatsoever regarding the quality, fitness for purpose, completeness, merchantability, non-infringement or accuracy of the Software, the Website and the Fantasy Cricket games. Stumps11 makes no warranty that its Software, Website, Games or Servers shall be uninterrupted, timely or error-free, that defects shall be corrected or that the features and Services provided therein shall be free from viruses or bugs of any kind. Stumps11 reserves the right to determine, at its sole discretion, whether it is responsible for any malfunction or disruption. Stumps11 reserves the right to limit your tournament/game participation or terminate your account in case it determines that you have intentionally caused such a malfunction or disruption. Stumps11 is not liable for any potential winnings from any unfinished tournaments or unfinished online Fantasy Cricket games.</string>
    <string name="UseofSoftware">Commercial use of our Software is strictly forbidden. Users are only allowed to use the Software for their personal entertainment. Under no circumstances shall Users be permitted to use their accounts on Stumps11.com for any purpose other than playing the Games for entertainment. Users may not attempt to modify, decompile, reverse-engineer or disassemble the Software in any way. The use of artificial intelligence including, without limitation, robots is strictly forbidden in connection with the Software and the Games. All actions taken in relation to Fantasy Cricket games by Users must be executed personally by Users using the user interface accessible through the Software.</string>
    <string name="LoginPrivacy">After you have registered on our Website or app, it is solely your responsibility to keep your Login Details absolutely confidential. Make sure you do not share your OTP with anybody, be it your family, friends or anyone else. We are not responsible in any way if your user account is logged in or accessed by anybody else using your mobile number.</string>
    <string name="EligibilityandJurisdictionPolicy">1. Our Contests are open only to persons aged 18 or older.
<br></br>
2. The Contests are open only to persons residing in India at the time of participation.
<br></br>
3. Stumps11 may, in accordance with the laws prevailing in certain Indian states, bar people who reside in certain Indian states from participating in any Contests. Currently people who reside in the Indian states of Assam, Odisha, Telangana, Nagaland, Sikkim &amp; Andhra Pradesh may not participate in any paid or cash Contests, as the laws of these states bar their residents from participating in any online games where participants are required to pay to enter contests like Fantasy Cricket rooms.
<br></br>
4. Every person who wishes to participate in the Contests must have a valid phone number.
<br></br>
5. Only those participants who have successfully registered on Stumps11.com as well as registered for a Contest prior to its each round in accordance with the rules outlined above shall be eligible to participate in the Contest and win prizes.</string>
    <string name="BreachandConsequences">In the event of breach of any of our Terms of Service, evidenced by our investigation, or if there is reasonable belief that your continued access to our Website is detrimental to the interests of Stumps11 Fantasy Cricket, our other Users or the general public, we may, at our sole discretion, take any or all of the following actions:
    <br></br>
        1. Restrict games between users suspected of colluding or cheating.
<br></br>
        2. Permanently freeze your user account on the Website.
        <br></br>
        3. Seize the money in your user account.
        <br></br>
        4. Demand damages for breach and take appropriate civil action to recover such damages, and/or initiate prosecution for violations that amount to offences in law.
        <br></br>
        5. Additionally, in the event of a material breach thereof, we reserve the right to bar you from future registration on the Website. The decision of Stumps11 Management on the action to be taken as a consequence of breach shall be final and binding on you. Any action taken by Stumps11 Fantasy Cricket platform shall be without prejudice to our other rights and remedies available in law or equity.
    </string>
    <string name="GoverningLawDisputeResolutionandJurisdiction">This Agreement shall in all respects be governed and interpreted and construed in accordance with the laws of India. All disputes, differences, complaints, etc. shall be subject to arbitration under the Indian Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996.</string>
    <string name="Content">All content and material on the Website, including, but not limited to, information, images, marks, logos, designs, pictures, graphics, text content, hyperlinks, multimedia clips, animation, games and software (collectively referred to as "Content" hereinafter), whether or not belonging to Stumps11, are protected by applicable intellectual property laws. Additionally, all chat content, messages, images, recommendations, emails, images sent by any Users can be logged/recorded by us and shall form part of Content and Stumps11 Fantasy Cricket platform is free to use this material in any manner whatsoever.
<br></br>
        Our Website may contain information about or hyperlinks to third parties. In such cases, we are not in any way responsible for the content on such websites, and we do not provide any express or implied warranty of the accuracy, completeness, suitability or quality of the content belonging to such third-party websites. You may choose to rely on any third-party content (content that does not belong to Stumps11) posted on our Website solely at your own risk and liability.
        <br></br>
        If you visit a third-party website through any third-party content posted on Stumps11.com, you will be subject to the terms and conditions applicable to that content. We neither control nor are we responsible for the content published on such third-party websites. The existence of a link to a third-party website on our Website is not in any way an endorsement of that website by us.
    </string>
    <string name="PublicContest">1. In the Public Contest format, Stumps11 may offer Contests comprising 2 Participants, 3 Participants, 5 Participants, 10 Pa
    ticipants, 100 Participants, or any other pre-designated number of Participants.
<br></br>
2. Stumps11 may offer this format of Contests as a paid format and the winner will be determined at the end of the round.
<br></br>
3. The number of Participants required to make a Contest operational will be pre-specified and once the number of Participants in such Contests equals the pre-specified number required for that Contest, the Contest shall be operational. In case the number of Participants is less than the pre-specified number at the pre-decided time of commencement of the round, such Contests shall not be operational and the Participation Fee paid by each Participant shall be credited back to the account of each User without any charge or deduction. In certain Contests across Stumps11 Services, designated as "Confirmed Contests", the Contests shall become operational once the number of Participants in such Contests equals the pre-specified number of winners to be declared in such Contests, even if all the available Participant slots (as pre-specified in relation to the Contests) remain unfilled. It is clarified that notwithstanding the activation of such Contests, Participants can continue to join such Contests until (i) all the available Participant slots in such Contests are filled, or (ii) the rounds to which the Contests relate commence, whichever is earlier. In case such Contests are not operational by the time of the commencement of the round, the Participation Fee paid by each Participant shall be credited back to the account of such User(s) without any charge or deduction.</string>
    <string name="Indemnity">To the extent permitted by law, and in consideration for being allowed to use our Services and participate in our Contests, you hereby agree to indemnify, save and hold harmless and defend us (to the extent of all benefits and awards, cost of litigation, disbursements and reasonable attorney\'s fees that we may incur in connection therewith including any direct, indirect or consequential losses, any loss of profit and loss of reputation) from any claims, actions, suits, taxes, damages, injuries, causes of action, penalties, interest, demands, expenses and/or awards asserted or brought against us by any person in connection with:
<br></br>
1. infringement of their intellectual property rights by your publication of any Content on our Website;
<br></br>
2. defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any other player or for anything that turns out to be misleading, inaccurate, defamatory, threatening, obscene or otherwise illegal whether originating from another player or otherwise;
<br></br>
3. use, abuse or misuse of your user account on our online Fantasy Cricket Website in any manner whatsoever;
<br></br>
4. any disconnections, technical failures, system breakdowns, defects, delays, interruptions, manipulated or improper data transmission, loss or corruption of data or communication lines failure, distributed denial of service attacks, viruses or any other adverse technological occurrences arising in connection with your access to or use of our Website;
<br></br>
5. access of your user account by any other person accessing the Services using your username or password, whether or not with your authorization.</string>
    <string name="GoverningLawandJurisdiction">Our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy shall be interpreted in accordance with the laws of India. Any dispute, controversy or claim arising from our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the civil courts at New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="Refund">All deposits and purchases made and fees paid on Stumps11.com to play or in connection with Fantasy Cricket are final. All transactions are final. We recognize that customer satisfaction is extremely important to us, so only error-oriented transaction cases shall be reviewed.
<br></br>
        <br></br>
If you are not fully satisfied with any deposit/purchase made or fee paid on Stumps11 and feel there is an \'Error’ in the transaction, please let us know about that within 3 days from the transaction date, and we shall certainly review the transaction and determine the resolution at our own discretion.
<br></br>
        <br></br>
Stumps11 reserves the right to cancel any matches for any reason, with or without disclosure of the reason, and refund all fees paid for such matches by any and all users.
<br></br>
        <br></br>
Stumps11 forbids Users from joining any game rooms after a cricket match related to the game room (identified by the Series) has begun.</string>
    <string name="Legality1">Playing games of skill is legal as it is excluded from the ambit of Indian gambling legislations, including the Public Gambling Act of 1867.The Supr

    e Court of India, in the cases of State of Andhra Pradesh v. K Satyanarayana (AIR 1968 SC 825) and KR Lakshmanan v. State of Tamil Nadu (AIR 1996 SC 1153), has held that a game in which success depends predominantly upon the superior knowledge, training, attention, experience and adroitness of the player shall be classified as a game of skill.
<br></br>
The Contents provided by Stumps11, described above, are games of skill as Participants’ success in the games depends primarily on their superior knowledge of the game of cricket  knowledge of players\' relative form, players\' performance in a particular territory, conditions and/or format (such as ODIs, Test Cricket and Twenty20 in the cricket fantasy game), attention and dedication to the Contests in which they are participating and adroitness in playing the Contests. The Contests also require Participants to field well-balanced sides with limited resources and make substitutions at appropriate times to gain the maximum points.
<br></br>
By participating in our Contests, each Participant acknowledges and agrees that he/she is participating in a game of skill, not chance.</string>
    <string name="FantasyScoreandFeeds">Stumps11 Fantasy Cricket platform may obtain the score feed and other information required for the computation and tabulation of score points from third party service provider(s). In the rare event that any error in the computation or tabulation of score points, selection of winners, etc. as a result of inaccuracy or incompleteness of the feed provided by the third-party service provider comes to its attention, Stumps11.com shall make best efforts to rectify such error prior to the distribution of prizes. However, Stumps11.com hereby clarifies that it relies on the accuracy and completeness of such third party score/statistic feeds and does not itself warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy thereof and, in any event, shall take no responsibility for inaccuracies in computation and tabulation of score points or the selection of winners as a result of any inaccurate or incomplete scores/statistics received from such third party service providers. Users and Participants agree not to make any claim or raise any complaint against Stumps11 in this respect.
<br></br>
In Starting Lineup Feature : Purpose of indicating a player\'s inclusion in final starting lineup is only to provide information and assist a user in selecting his/her team on Stumps11. While indicating a Player\'s inclusion in starting lineup is given by Stumps11 on the basis of information/data received through feed providers, publicly available information. Users are advised to do a thorough research of their own from official sources and/or other available sources of information. Stumps11, shall not take any liability, if a player earlier indicated as \'Playing\' does not play or start for any reason whatsoever.
<br></br>
Bonuses: The following conditions apply to all the Fantasy Cricket Bonuses and Promotions/Offers (Instant Bonus, Friend Referral Bonus, Free Bonus, Earnings Bonus) on www.stumps11.com and all Users who receive a Bonus or Promotion amount are bound by them:
<br></br>
Free Bonus: This is a bonus that first goes into your Bonus account and then gradually from your Bonus Account to your Balance Account as you join game rooms and pay the match fee. The bonus is released at 10% of the Match Fee for every Fantasy Cricket room you join, pay the match fee and stand a winner or loser in the game, i.e. the game finishes.
<br></br>
Friend Referral Bonus: This bonus is like an instant bonus. For every friend you refer who plays a cash game on Stumps11.com (deposits money, joins and wins or loses in a cash game room), we give you an Instant Bonus for referring that friend.
<br></br>
Free Money Prize: This is an offer that allows you to play a game without paying any entry fee at all but you can win a cash prize in this room. For example, you can join a Rs. 500 prize room with no entry fee and win the cash prize.</string>
    <string name="BonusesTermsandConditions">1. Deposit Bonuses are added to this bucket
<br></br>
2. Promotional winnings (Winnings at contests) are added to this bucket
<br></br>
3. The Sign-up Bonus and Referral Bonuses, are added to this bucket
<br></br>
4. The user cannot withdraw cash from this bucket
<br></br>
Score
<br></br>
1. This is moved to Winnings/Withdrawable bucket only when the user converts to a cash player (Deposits cash &amp; play a cash game)</string>
    <string name="Prizes">1. A User can win only one prize in a day.
<br></br>
2. In the scenario of a User winning multiple prize rooms in a day, the User will win the prize for the first room that he/she joined on that particular day. The Users with the second-highest points in the other game rooms will win the prizes.
<br></br>
3. Every User is allowed only one entry in any Free Entry-based Prize Money or Prize Item room. You are not allowed to enter our Fantasy Cricket rooms using multiple accounts.
<br></br>
4. Freight and shipping charges and customs duties on all prizes shall be borne by the winners.
<br></br>
5. All prizes shall be subject to tax deduction (TDS) as per the Income Tax Act 1961. Winners will be provided TDS certificates in respect of such tax deductions. Winners shall be responsible for payment of any other applicable taxes, including, but not limited to, the income tax and gift tax in respect of the prize money.
<br></br>
6. We do not consider any changes made to the scorecard once the settlement is done.
<br></br>
7. By downloading and/or using the licensed Stumps11 application, you acknowledge and agree to the following:
<br></br>
8. Stumps11, its subsidiaries and all group companies that collectively come under the name Stumps11 are in no way responsible for the application and the content within. Also, your use of this application and Website is limited to a non-transferable personal use.
<br></br>
9. Stumps11 has no obligation of warranty with respect to the Website or Content on it. All claims, liabilities, losses, damages, costs and/or expenses that occur because of using Stumps11 Products, Services, Website or the Content on it are the sole responsibility of the User. Stumps11 is not responsible to address claims relating to the Website and/or your use of the Website or the Products and Services available on it.
<br></br>
10. We allow people from all the states and union territories of India, except Assam, Odisha, Telangana, Karnataka, Nagaland, Sikkim &amp; Andhra Pradesh, to play Fantasy Cricket games on Stumps11.
<br></br>
11. All the standard terms and conditions of Stumps11 apply.
<br></br>
12. The decision of Stumps11 Management shall be final and binding in case of any dispute.</string>
</resources>